[
  {
    "question": "Polska",
    "answer": "Warszawa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Niemcy",
    "answer": "Berlin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Francja",
    "answer": "Paryż"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wielka Brytania",
    "answer": "Londyn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hiszpania",
    "answer": "Madryt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Włochy",
    "answer": "Rzym"
  },
  {
    "question": "Czechy",
    "answer": "Praga"
  },
  {
    "question": "Norwegia",
    "answer": "Oslo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Szwecja",
    "answer": "Sztokholm"
  },
  {
    "question": "Grecja",
    "answer": "Ateny"
  },
  {
    "question": "Portugalia",
    "answer": "Lizbona"
  },
  {
    "question": "Irlandia",
    "answer": "Dublin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Holandia",
    "answer": "Amsterdam"
  },
  {
    "question": "Belgia",
    "answer": "Bruksela"
  },
  {
    "question": "Szwajcaria",
    "answer": "Berno"
  },
  {
    "question": "Austria",
    "answer": "Wiedeń"
  }
]